Guide to the Artists Space Archive MSS.291
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series III: Administrative Files, 1973 - 2007
  - Subseries A: Gallery Organization
    - Artists Space Insurance Policy (Fine Art), 2005 - 2007 (Box 103, Folder 6)
    - Arts Benefit All Coalition Alternative (ABACA): "Arts Reflection Has No Complexion, While Racial Tension Creates Art Inventions", 2005 (Box 103, Folder 7)
    - "Curatorial": Exhibition Schedule, Dan Shipsides Materials, 2005 (Box 103, Folder 8)
    - Donations [No Access], 2005 (Box 103, Folder 9)
      Conditions Governing Access
      Access of these financial records is restricted. For more information, contact a Fales archivist.
    - Donations for Online Upgrade, 2005 (Box 103, Folder 10)
    - Duty and Customs Information, Notes, 2005 - 2007 (Box 103, Folder 11)
    - Exhibition Loans (EDITIONS), 2005 (Box 103, Folder 12)
    - Exhibition Profit and Loss Details, Budget Reports, 2005 - 2006 (Box 103, Folder 13)
    - New Artists Space Specifications and Information, 2005 (Box 103, Folder 14)
    - Poker at Parker's Box, 2005 (Box 103, Folder 15)
    - "Recent Publications File," Philippe Parreno, 2005 - 2007 (Box 104, Folder 1)
    - Armory Art Fair - Correspondence, Adam McEwen Calendar, 2006 (Box 104, Folder 2)
    - Calendars, August 2005 - July 2009 (Box 104, Folder 3)
    - Curatorial Meeting Agendas and Notes, 2006 - 2007 (Box 104, Folder 4)
    - Independent Projects Grant, 2006 (Box 104, Folder 5)
    - Spring Benefit, 2006 (Box 104, Folder 6)
    - Staff Meeting Materials, 2006 (Box 104, Folder 7)
    - Video Digitization, 2006 (Box 104, Folder 8)
    - Beckelman and Capalino Artists Space Board Presentation, May 7, 2007 (Box 104, Folder 9)
    - Funding Notes, 2007 (Box 104, Folder 10)
    - Independent Project Grant: Eugenie Tung, 2007 (Box 104, Folder 11)
    - Archival Planning and Research, 2009 (Box 104, Folder 12)
    - Eastern Long Island Driving Map, undated (Box 104, Folder 13)
    - Exhibition History, 2009 (Box 104, Folder 14)
    - Artists Space Logo Mock-Ups, Undated Administrative (Box 104, Folder 15)
    - Barbara Bloom: Correspondence, Source Materials, undated (Box 104, Folder 16)
    - Chuck Close Daguerre Images, undated (Box 104, Folder 17)
    - Condition Report Templates, undated (Box 104, Folder 18)
    - Director of Exhibitions Position Overview, undated (Box 104, Folder 19)
    - Events, Exhibitions, Publications Master Lists [1 of 2], undated (Box 104, Folder 20)
    - Events, Exhibitions, Publications Master Lists [2 of 2], undated (Box 104, Folder 21)
    - Press Kit Templates, undated (Box 104, Folder 22)
    - Registrar Handbook, undated (Box 104, Folder 23)
  - Subseries B: Workshops
    - Art in Transit: Tips for Safeguarding Your Artwork, 2003 (Box 104, Folder 24)
    - The Artist-Dealer Connection, 2003 (Box 104, Folder 25)
    - Fear Factor, c. 2003 (Box 104, Folder 26)
    - Secrets to Successful Slides: Photographing Artwork, 2003 (Box 105, Folder 1)
    - Survival Skills Series, 2003 - 2005 (Box 105, Folder 2)
    - Workshops: Notes and Research, 2003 - 2006 (Box 105, Folder 3)
    - Leaving the Nest, 2004 (Box 105, Folder 4)
    - No More Slides: Ways to Present Your Artwork Digitally to Curators, 2004 (Box 105, Folder 5)
    - The Perfect Packet: Artists Resumes, Statements, Cover Letters, 2004 (Box 105, Folder 6)
    - Protect Yourself: Copyright Issues and Fairuse for Artists, 2004 (Box 105, Folder 7)
    - Reading Between the Lines, 2004 (Box 105, Folder 8)
    - Studio Savvy, 2004 (Box 105, Folder 9)
    - What's It All Worth? How to Value Your Artwork, 2004 - 2005 (Box 105, Folder 10)
    - The Young and the Talented: Gallery Representation of Young Artists, 2004 - 2005 (Box 105, Folder 11)
    - Beyond the Canvas: Working as an Experimental Media Artist, 2005 (Box 105, Folder 12)
    - Declare Your Independence: Independent Curating Now, 2005 (Box 105, Folder 13)
    - Express Yourself: Tips on Writing Artists Statements, 2005 (Box 105, Folder 14)
    - Selling Without Selling Out: Tools on How to Promote Your Artwork, 2005 (Box 105, Folder 15)
    - Ways and Means: Managing Projects, Budgets, and Production Schedules, 2005 (Box 105, Folder 16)
    - The Art of the Contract, 2006 (Box 105, Folder 17)
    - Contracts and Cyberspace: Internet Do's and Don'ts for Artists, 2006 (Box 105, Folder 18)
    - Individual Artist Funding Made Simple, 2006 (Box 105, Folder 19)
    - It's a Steal: Copyright Basics for Visual Arts, 2006 (Box 105, Folder 20)
    - Making Positive Changes, 2006 (Box 105, Folder 21)
    - The New Artists File Online Revised, 2006 (Box 105, Folder 22)
    - The Perfect Packet II, 2006 (Box 105, Folder 23)
    - Visiting Artists, 2006 (Box 105, Folder 24)
    - Young Collectors, 2006 (Box 105, Folder 25)
    - Protecting Your Artwork on the Internet: Copyright Basics, 2007 (Box 105, Folder 26)
    - So You Got The Studio Visit, Now What?, 2007 (Box 106, Folder 1)
    - Upcoming Workshops, 2007 (Box 106, Folder 2)
    - Website 101: What Every Artists Needs to Know to Get Their Work Online, 2007 (Box 106, Folder 3)
    - Financial Advice, Planning for Emerging Artists, undated (Box 106, Folder 4)
    - Workshop Research [1 of 3], various (Box 106, Folder 5)
    - Workshop Research [2 of 3], various (Box 106, Folder 6)
    - Workshop Research [3 of 3], various (Box 106, Folder 7)
- Series IV: Book Files, 1988 - 1998
  These materials are arranged alphabetically, then chronologically. This series includes documentation generated by the research, fundraising, and production of the never-produced 15th anniversary book, intended to be published in 1988. In addition, this series preserves materials generated by the production of the 25th anniversary book published in 1998, 5000 Artists Return to Artists Space: 25 Years. This book is available at Fales. It is clear that the 25th anniversary book relied heavily on research materials originally generated by the production of the 15th anniversary book. The materials in this series include drafts, budgets, correspondence, notes, images, funding sources, brochures, catalogs, slides, interview typescripts, chronology, notes, and other research materials.
  - 15th Anniversary Catalogue, 1988 - 1989 (Box 106, Folder 8)
  - 15th Anniversary Publication Materials, 1989 (Box 106, Folder 9)
  - 25th Anniversary Book: Articles/Essays by Trudie Grace and Thomas Lawson, 1997 (Box 106, Folder 10)
  - 25th Anniversary Book: Chronology [1 of 3], 1996 (Box 106, Folder 11)
  - 25th Anniversary Book: Chronology [2 of 3], 1996 (Box 106, Folder 12)
  - 25th Anniversary Book: Chronology [3 of 3], 1996 (Box 106, Folder 13)
  - 25th Anniversary Book: Chronology, 1997 (Box 107, Folder 1)
  - 25th Anniversary Book: Debi Sonzogni, Debra Singer, 1996 - 1998 (Box 107, Folder 2)
  - 25th Anniversary Book: Design Writing Research, 1998 (Box 107, Folder 3)
  - 25th Anniversary Book: Library of Congress Research, Memos, Correspondence, 1996 - 1998 (Box 107, Folder 4)
  - 25th Anniversary Book: Schedules, Status, 1998 (Box 107, Folder 5)
  - 35 Artists Return To Artists Space: A Benefit Exhibition, 1981 - 1982 (Box 107, Folder 6)
  - "The 1990's" Interview Excerpts, Notes, undated (Box 107, Folder 7)
  - 5000 Artists Return to Artists Space: 25 Years - Book Party Postcards, Slides, April 20, 1999 (Box 107, Folder 8)
  - 5000 Artists Return to Artists Space: 25 Years - Correspondence with Babette Mangolte, 1998 (Box 107, Folder 9)
  - 5000 Artists Return to Artists Space: 25 Years - Front Matter, 1998 (Box 107, Folder 10)
  - 5000 Artists Return to Artists Space: 25 Years - Press Releases, 1998 (Box 107, Folder 11)
  - Artists Slide File: Synopsis of Proposed Services, [1997] (Box 107, Folder 12)
  - Artists Space 25th Anniversary Year: Exhibition Program Overview, 1998 (Box 107, Folder 13)
  - Artists Space: Celebrating 25 Years at The Museum of Modern Art - Postcard, Slides, 1998 - 1999 (Box 107, Folder 14)
  - Artists Space Activities "Updated", February 24, 1989 (Box 107, Folder 15)
  - Artists Space Activities Master List, April 3, 1989 (Box 107, Folder 16)
  - Artists Space Activities, April 8, 1989 (Box 107, Folder 17)
  - Artists Space Activities "Given to Kathy Peck", April 8, 1989 (Box 107, Folder 18)
  - Artists Space Activities, May 27, 1989 (Box 107, Folder 19)
  - Artists Space Activities, May 27, 1989 (Box 108, Folder 1)
  - Artists Space Activities, May 27, 1989 (Box 108, Folder 2)
  - Artists Space Activities, undated (Box 108, Folder 3)
  - Artists Space Activities "Early Version", 1989 - 1991 (Box 108, Folder 4)
  - Artists Space Activities, [1988 - 1991] (Box 108, Folder 5)
  - Artists Space Activities "Obsolete Draft", 1989 (Box 108, Folder 6)
  - Artists Space Publications List, [1991] (Box 108, Folder 7)
  - Benefit and Membership Information, 1983 - 1997 (Box 108, Folder 8)
  - Benefit Multiples, 1991 (Box 108, Folder 9)
  - "Blurb on Artists Grants and Artists File", [1988 - 1991] (Box 108, Folder 10)
  - "Board History According to Director's Tenure", [1998] (Box 108, Folder 11)
  - Board of Directors Lists, 1992 - 1996 (Box 108, Folder 12)
  - Book Production Materials [1 of 2], [1989] (Box 108, Folder 13)
  - Book Production Materials [2 of 2], 1989 (Box 109, Folder 1)
  - Catalogue - 15th Anniversary: Old Notes 1986-1989, Findings, Estimates (Box 109, Folder 2)
  - "Catalogue Originals", 1989 (Box 109, Folder 3)
  - "Chronology Materials Added In", 1998 (Box 109, Folder 4)
  - Claudia Gould Acknowledgments, Valerie Smith Editorial Notes, 1998 (Box 109, Folder 5)
  - Content of "Sound Selections," Installation Instructions, Loan Forms, undated (Box 109, Folder 6)
  - "Copy Editors and Indexes", 1998 (Box 109, Folder 7)
  - Corrected Interviews, undated (Box 109, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence with Artists Regarding Interviews, 1998 (Box 109, Folder 9)
  - Directors Interviews - Helene Winer (Includes Correspondence), 1998 (Box 109, Folder 10)
  - Directors Interviews - Linda Shearer Correspondence, 1998 (Box 109, Folder 11)
  - Directors Interviews - Susan Wyatt Interviewed by Evelyn Leong (Includes Correspondence), 1998 (Box 109, Folder 12)
  - Distributed Art Publishers, 1998 (Box 109, Folder 13)
  - [Draft], undated (Box 109, Folder 14)
  - Events and Exhibition Flyers, [1989] (Box 109, Folder 15)
  - Events and Exhibitions Lists, undated (Box 109, Folder 16)
  - Exhibiting Artists Lists, 1988-1997 (Box 109, Folder 17)
  - Exhibition Brochures and Mailers, 1990 - 1991 (Box 109, Folder 18)
  - Fact Checking Notes, [1998] (Box 109, Folder 19)
  - February Panels at Artists Space - Invoices, Notes, Slides, 1999 (Box 109, Folder 20)
  - "Film and Video Catalogues, Brochures: Nancy and Dan's Highlights", various (Box 109, Folder 21)
  - "Front Matter and Current Board" - Artists Space Documentary Catalogue, 1991 (Box 110, Folder 1)
  - Funders/Donors, 1991 (Box 110, Folder 2)
  - Funding History, [1997] (Box 110, Folder 3)
  - History of Benefit Multiples, 1997 (Box 110, Folder 4)
  - "History of the Emergency Materials Fund and The Independent Exhibitions Program, 1973-1981", [1998] (Box 110, Folder 5)
  - "History of the Irving Sandler Artists' File", [1998] (Box 110, Folder 6)
  - Interview Drafts [1 of 3], 1997 - 1998 (Box 110, Folder 7)
  - Interview Drafts [2 of 3], 1997 - 1998 (Box 110, Folder 8)
  - Interview Drafts [3 of 3], 1997 - 1998 (Box 110, Folder 9)
  - Interview Index, April 5, 1998 (Box 110, Folder 10)
  - Interview with Claudia Gould, April 1997 (Box 110, Folder 11)
  - Inventory (Witnesses), 1989 (Box 110, Folder 12)
  - Jenny Holzer Studio - Correspondence, 1998 (Box 110, Folder 13)
  - "Last 2 Years of Chronology", 1991 (Box 110, Folder 14)
  - Letter of Agreement, October 4, 1988 (Box 110, Folder 15)
  - Limited Multiples - Correspondence, Price Lists, 1988 - 1991 (Box 110, Folder 16)
  - Logos - Philip Morris, National Endowment For The Arts, 1998 (Box 110, Folder 17)
  - Master: Artists Space Activities, March 16, 1989 (Box 111, Folder 1)
  - "Master for Proposed Design," Administrative, Financial, 1989 - 1991 (Box 111, Folder 2)
  - The Membership Program, 1997 (Box 111, Folder 3)
  - Multiples Sent For Membership, 1987 - 1989 (Box 111, Folder 4)
  - "Nancy's Essay, Excerpts, Interviews", undated (Box 111, Folder 5)
  - National Endowment for the Arts Supplemental Material, 1983 (Box 111, Folder 6)
  - New York State Council on the Arts Support, 1973-78, 1998 (Box 111, Folder 7)
  - "Notes on Chronology - Queries and Answers", 1989 (Box 111, Folder 8)
  - Old Drafts of Chronology [1 of 2], 1997 - 1998 (Box 111, Folder 9)
  - Old Drafts of Chronology [2 of 2], 1997 - 1998 (Box 111, Folder 10)
  - Old Drafts of Chronology With Corrections, 1997 - 1998 (Box 111, Folder 11)
  - Open Call Lists, undated (Box 112, Folder 1)
  - Open Video Call, June 1997 (Box 112, Folder 2)
  - "Open Video Call 10 February 1998 (For Valerie)" (Box 112, Folder 3)
  - "Outline of Artists Spaces' 15 Year Catalogue", 1988 - 1989 (Box 112, Folder 4)
  - "Photo Doc + Chronology Notes", [1988-1991] (Box 112, Folder 5)
  - Photo Documentation Correspondence, 1998 (Box 112, Folder 6)
  - Photographs, 1986, undated (Box 112, Folder 7)
  - Photographs and Negatives, 1986, undated (Box 112, Folder 8)
  - Photographs with Order Form, 1989 (Box 112, Folder 9)
  - Publications History, 1997 (Box 112, Folder 10)
  - Publishing Research, Notes, 1998 (Box 112, Folder 11)
  - "Raw Material to Input Special Events, Events Committee Lists", 1989 (Box 112, Folder 12)
  - "Recent Schedules to Use to Fact Check", 1991 (Box 112, Folder 13)
  - Report on Donations, June 1989 (Box 112, Folder 14)
  - Slide File Marathons Flyers, undated (Box 112, Folder 15)
  - Staff History, 1998 (Box 112, Folder 16)
  - Staff History - Drafts, 1998 (Box 112, Folder 17)
  - Staff History - Phone Lists (Drafts), Correspondence, 1998 (Box 112, Folder 18)
  - Susan Wyatt [1 of 3], 1998 (Box 112, Folder 19)
  - Susan Wyatt [2 of 3], 1998 (Box 113, Folder 1)
  - Susan Wyatt [3 of 3], [1989] (Box 113, Folder 2)
  - Video Programming Brochures, Programs, Press Releases, [1997] (Box 113, Folder 3)
  - Room 207: Taka Iimura - Japan Film/Video Newspaper [2 of 2], March 27, 1977 (Box 122, Folder 3)
- Series V: Independent Project Grants, 1979 - 2005; 1998-2005
  This series consists of materials generated by the Independent Project Grant program administered by Artists Space. These grants were provided to artists to stage exhibitions, either solo or in groups. These were available to unrepresented New York artists to put on shows in non-commercial spaces in the New York area. The material consists of grant proposals, work samples, correspondence, and documentation of grant spending, budgeting and planning.
  This series is arranged chronologically, and alphabetically within each year.
  - Independent Exhibitions Program, Emergency Materials Fund, Independent Project Grants Program (IPG), 1979 - 1991 (Box 113, Folder 4)
  - Applications, Correspondence, 1998 - 1999 (Box 113, Folder 5)
  - Artists' Resumes, Correspondence, January 1999 (Box 113, Folder 6)
  - Applications, Correspondence, April 1999 (Box 113, Folder 7)
  - Artist List, Applications, October 1999 (Box 113, Folder 8)
  - Artist Recipients Lists, 1999 - 2000 (Box 113, Folder 9)
  - Artists' Applications, Correspondence, January 2000 (Box 113, Folder 10)
  - Artists' Applications, Correspondence, April 2000 (Box 113, Folder 11)
  - Tzvi Bern-Aretz, October 2000 (Box 113, Folder 12)
  - Artists' Applications, Correspondence, January 2001 (Box 113, Folder 13)
  - Guidelines, Takuya Fukumoto Application, April 2001 (Box 113, Folder 14)
  - Artists' Applications, Correspondence, December 2001 (Box 113, Folder 15)
  - Leah Oates, 2001 (Box 113, Folder 16)
  - Artists' Applications, 2002 (Box 113, Folder 17)
  - Artists' Applications, April 2002 (Box 114, Folder 1)
  - Jon Birdseye, Summer 2002 (Box 114, Folder 2)
  - Artists' Applications [1 of 2], 2002 - 2003 (Box 114, Folder 3)
  - Artists' Applications [2 of 2], 2002 - 2003 (Box 114, Folder 4)
  - 2001 - 2003 Recipients List (Box 114, Folder 5)
  - Artists' Applications, 2003 (Box 114, Folder 6)
  - Artists' Applications, September 2003 (Box 114, Folder 7)
  - Danielle Dimston, November 2003 (Box 114, Folder 8)
  - Guidelines, Application, Rejection Letter Templates, 2003 (Box 114, Folder 9)
  - Hosok Chung, November 2003 (Box 114, Folder 10)
  - James Jaxxa, November 2003 (Box 114, Folder 11)
  - Kelli Anderson, November 2003 (Box 114, Folder 12)
  - Thiago Szmrecsanyi, November 2003 (Box 114, Folder 13)
  - "No Non-Profit Letter", 2003 - 2004 (Box 114, Folder 14)
  - Christina Ray, February 2004 (Box 114, Folder 15)
  - Clifford Borress, February 2004 (Box 114, Folder 16)
  - Continuous Project (collective), June 2004 (Box 114, Folder 17)
  - Jed Ela, February 2004 (Box 114, Folder 18)
  - Manifold/Eric Worcester, 2004 - 2005 (Box 114, Folder 19)
  - Marie Lorenz, February 2004 (Box 114, Folder 20)
  - Tamara Gubernat, June 2004 (Box 114, Folder 21)
  - Mika Tajima, September 2004 (Box 114, Folder 22)
  - Eugenie Tung, February 2005 (Box 114, Folder 23)
  - Elana Langer, April 2005 (Box 114, Folder 24)
  - Glowlab (Christina Ray), Elaine Gan, June 2005 (Box 114, Folder 25)
  - Dona Stern, June 2005 (Box 114, Folder 26)
  - Elaine Kaufmann, October 2005 (Box 115, Folder 1)
  - Melissa Brown, November 2005 (Box 115, Folder 2)
- Series VI: Curator Files, 1979 - 2007
  This series includes the administrative files of both Lauri Firstenberg and Christian Rattemeyer relating to exhibitions that they curated. The material Includes slides, cvs, correspondence, and other files related to exhibition planning.
  The archivist followed the chronological arrangement for this series, and arranged the files alphabetically within years for clarity. The files were removed from their original binders for preservation purposes, and the folder titles note this.
  - Candace Clement: Artist's Resume, Correspondence, 1979 (Box 115, Folder 3)
  - Ray Johnson: Press Clippings, 1979 (Box 115, Folder 4)
  - Eric Bogosian: Advocate Performance Photocopy, December 8, 1982 (Box 115, Folder 5)
  - Laurie Simmons: Artist's Resume, Press, Projected Budget, 1996 (Box 115, Folder 6)
  - Mark Flood: Artist's Materials, 1996 (Box 115, Folder 7)
  - Emerging Curator Series: Kaye Donachie - Correspondence, Resume, 1998, 2003 (Box 115, Folder 8)
  - Makow Drawing Project Space: Photographs, Press, Correspondence [1 of 2], 1998 - 2002 (Box 115, Folder 9)
  - Makow Drawing Project Space: Press, Proposal, Slides [2 of 2], 1998 - 2002 (Box 115, Folder 10)
  - Jeanne van Heeswijk: Correspondence, 1999 (Box 115, Folder 11)
  - Albrecht Schafer: "Arbeiten 97-01," " Berlin Alexanderplatz", [2001] (Box 115, Folder 12)
  - Albrecht Schafer: Malewitsch Museum Biberach, "Styropor," Works 1997 - 2003, 2001, 2003 (Box 115, Folder 13)
  - Curatorial Projects: Kevin McHugh, [2002] (Box 115, Folder 14)
  - L.E.FT Architects, Odile Decq, 2002 - 2003 (Box 115, Folder 15)
  - Painting As Paradox: Catalogue Photocopies, November 7, 2002 (Box 115, Folder 16)
  - Albrecht Schafer: Exhibition Administrative, Budget, 2003 - 2004 (Box 115, Folder 17)
  - An Te Liu, Reiser + Umemoto RUR Architecture P.C., 2003 (Box 116, Folder 1)
  - Dee Williams: "Berlin Street Signs", [2003 - 2004] (Box 116, Folder 2)
  - "January 18 - February 22, Artists Space Project Spaces", 2003 (Box 116, Folder 3)
  - Artists Space Project Space: Artists' Materials, 2003 - 2004 (Box 116, Folder 4)
  - Katsuhiro Saiki: Budget, Correspondence, October 2003 (Box 116, Folder 5)
  - Artists Space Brochure Proofs, November 2003 (Box 116, Folder 6)
  - Superstudio: Administrative, Correspondence, [2003] (Box 116, Folder 7)
  - Superstudio: Archive, [2003] (Box 116, Folder 8)
  - Superstudio: Press, [2003] (Box 116, Folder 9)
  - William Pope.L: eRacism - Exhibition Administrative, 2003 (Box 116, Folder 10)
  - Artists Space Open Video Call - Artist List, 2004 (Box 116, Folder 11)
  - Robert Arndt: Artist's Resume, Correspondence, 2004 (Box 116, Folder 12)
  - Institute of Contemporary Art Boston: Made in Mexico - Checklist, Slides, January 21, 2004 (Box 116, Folder 13)
  - Establishing Shot: Catalogue Drafts, March 9, 2004 (Box 116, Folder 14)
  - Establishing Shot: Press, Promotional Drafts, March 9, 2004 (Box 116, Folder 15)
  - Harrell Fletcher: A Moment of Doubt - Exhibition Brochure, April 30, 2004 (Box 117, Folder 1)
  - Repeat Performance: Administrative, Promotional, May 20, 2004 (Box 117, Folder 2)
  - Repeat Performance: Catalogue Draft, May 20, 2004 (Box 117, Folder 3)
  - Benjamin Aranda: "Color Test - Proposal for a Very Large Sealed Glow", Spring 2004 (Box 117, Folder 4)
  - Megan McGinnis: Artists Slides, [2004] (Box 117, Folder 5)
  - Robin Rhode: Correspondence, Press, May 2004 (Box 117, Folder 6)
  - Based on a True Story: Administrative, Correspondence, September 14, 2004 (Box 117, Folder 7)
  - Based on a True Story: Catalogue Drafts, September 14, 2004 (Box 117, Folder 8)
  - openhousenewyork: Brochure, October 2004 (Box 117, Folder 9)
  - Architecture and Design Project Series - Sensual Hyper Tension: Odile Decq Correspondence, November 12, 2004 (Box 117, Folder 10)
  - Flipside: Exhibition Administrative, Correspondence, November 12, 2004 (Box 117, Folder 11)
  - World AIDS Day - Wooloo File, December 2004 (Box 117, Folder 12)
  - Architecture and Design Project Series - Swetlana Heger: Artist's Materials, January 18, 2005 (Box 117, Folder 13)
  - Architecture and Design Project Series: Correspondence, Notes, 2005 - 2006 (Box 117, Folder 14)
  - Sari Carel: Artist's Resume, Slides, [2005] (Box 117, Folder 15)
  - Log Cabin: Administrative, Correspondence, January 18, 2005 (Box 117, Folder 16)
  - Model Modernisms: Administrative, March 9, 2005 (Box 117, Folder 17)
  - Model Modernisms: Catalogue Drafts, March 9, 2005 (Box 117, Folder 18)
  - nArchitects - Party Wall: Correspondence, March 9, 2005 (Box 118, Folder 1)
  - Two Exhibitions Organized by Bard College's Center for Curatorial Studies: Administrative, May 2005 (Box 118, Folder 2)
  - Hunch and Flail: Administrative, June 21, 2005 (Box 118, Folder 3)
  - Hunch and Flail: Catalogue Photocopies, June 21, 2005 (Box 118, Folder 4)
  - Architecture and Design Project Series - Wild Walls New York, A Series of Films in/on Architecture: Administrative, September 16, 2005 (Box 118, Folder 5)
  - But it was all green - Ryan Gander, September 16, 2005 (Box 118, Folder 6)
  - International Geographic: Kelly Poe Correspondence, Images, September 16, 2005 (Box 118, Folder 7)
  - International Geographic - Raquel Ormella and Kelly Poe: Administrative, September 16, 2005 (Box 118, Folder 8)
  - La Villa Basque, Vernon, California - Adria Julia: Exhibition Expenses, Slides, September 16, 2005 (Box 118, Folder 9)
  - Artists Space Events - Exhibition Brochure Photocopy, November - December 2005 (Box 118, Folder 10)
  - Performa05 - 1st Biennial of New Visual Art Performance in New York City, November 2005 (Box 118, Folder 11)
  - Adam McEwen Calendar, 2006 (Box 118, Folder 12)
  - Bas Jan Ader, 2006 (Box 118, Folder 13)
  - Cecil Balmond Agu [H_edge: ARUP Advance Geometry Unit], 2006 (Box 118, Folder 14)
  - Daniel Toglar, [2006] (Box 118, Folder 15)
  - Leslie Hewitt: Note on Budget, [2006] (Box 118, Folder 16)
  - January-February Budgets, Carl Ferrero Slides, January - February 2006 (Box 118, Folder 17)
  - Simply Because You're Near Me - Jennie C. Jones: Artist's Materials, January 12, 2006 (Box 118, Folder 18)
  - Christian Rattemeyer Correspondence to Anne Lacaton and Jean Philippe Vassal, March 2, 2006 (Box 118, Folder 19)
  - When Artists Say We: Administrative, Promotional, March 8, 2006 (Box 119, Folder 1)
  - The Renaissance Society at The University of Chicago: Newsletter, May - June 2006 (Box 119, Folder 2)